Guide to the Marilyn Horne Foundation Records, 1991-2011 CTC.2010.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio/Visual Materials, 1995-2010; IV.
  - National Residency Program and other recordings, 1996-2001; 1.
    - Interview, January 12, 2010 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      Interview on the Leonard Lopate Show on the WYNC radio station.
      - WNYC radio broadcast, CD, 24 minutes
    - Recital, January 29, 2010 (Box 138, Folder 14)
      Huntsville Chamber Music Guild 10th Anniversary Recital at Trinity United Methodist Church, AL.
      Jonathan Beyer, baritone; Kristin Okerlund, piano.
      - Video recording, DVD, 87 minutes
    - Recital, January 30, 2010 (Box 138, Folder 15)
      Sidney Outlaw, baritone; Carol Wong, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 65 minutes
    - Board meeting, May 3, 2010 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - Audio recording, Cassette, 85 minutes
    - Audition (Box 138, Folder 17)
      Audition cassettee tape sent to the Mariyln Horne Foundation.
      Leon Williams, baritone.
      - Audio recording, Cassette, 22 minutes
    - Marilyn Horne tribute (Box 138, Folder 18)
      Marilyn Horne Foundation video shown during an annual recital.
      - Career retrospective, DVD, 9 minutes
    - Promotional video (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - Video recording, VHS, 23 minutes
    - Recital (Box 138, Folder 20)
      National Residency Program recital at unknown venue.
      - Video recording, VHS, 30 minutes
  - On Wings of Song, 1995-2010; 2.
    On Wings of Song is the Marilyn Horne Foundation's monthly vocal recital program which features young artists. These recordings are arranged in chronological order. Each performance contains a note with venue and artist information, the format of the recording, and the length.
    - 1995-1996 Season
      - Recital, October 5, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 1)
        On Wings of Song recital at the Kosciuszko Foundation House, NYC.
        Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation, the Kosciuszko Foundation, and WQXR-FM Radio.
        Michelle DeYoung, mezzo soprano; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 14, 1995; CD, 67 minutes
      - Recital, November 19, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 2)
        Marcus DeLoach, baritone; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 25, 1995; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, February 11, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 3)
        Earle Patriarco, baritone; David Clemensen, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 17, 1996; CD, 64 minutes
      - Recital, March 24, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 4)
        Wendy Hoffman, mezzo soprano; Brian Zeger, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 30, 1996; CD, 52 minutes
      - Recital, April 21, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 5)
        Pamela Pantos, mezzo soprano; Brian Zeger, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 4, 1996; CD, 51 minutes
      - Recital, May 19, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 6)
        Russell Braun, baritone; Carolyn Maule, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 25, 1996; CD, 71 minutes
    - 1996-1997 Season
      - Recital, September 29, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 7)
        Margaret Lattimore, mezzo soprano; Brian Zeger, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 5, 1996; CD, 74 minutes
      - Recital, October 20, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 8)
        Olga Makarina, soprano; Yelena Kurdina, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 26, 1996; CD, 72 minutes
      - Recital, November 17, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 9)
        Kenneth Robertson, baritone; DeWitt Tipton, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 23, 1996; CD, 70 minutes
      - Recital, December 15, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 10)
        Jane Jennings, soprano; Brian Garman, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 21, 1996; CD, 79 minutes
      - Recital, February 9, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 11)
        On Wings of Song recital at the Kosciuszko Foundation House, NYC. Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation, the Kosciuszko Foundation, and WQXR-FM Radio.
        Rinat Shaham, mezzo soprano; Mikael Eliasen, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 15, 1997; CD, 80 minutes
      - Recital, March 9, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 12)
        Christòpheren Nomura, baritone; Kayo Iwama, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 15, 1997; CD, 73 minutes
      - Recital, April 20, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 13)
        Stephanie Blythe, mezzo soprano; Marcus DeLoach, baritone; Olga Makarina, soprano; Penderecki String Quartet.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 3, 1997; 2 CDs, 78 minutes
      - Recital, May 18, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 14)
        Denis Sedov, bass; Rakefet Hak, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 24, 1997; CD, 69 minutes
    - 1997-1998 Season
      - Recital, September 28, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 15)
        Lynette Tapia, soprano; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 4, 1997; CD, 64 minutes
      - Recital, October 26, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 16)
        Mary Phillips, mezzo soprano; Ted Taylor, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 8, 1997; 2 CDs, 83 minutes
      - Recital, November 23, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 17)
        John Osborn, tenor; Brian Zeger, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 29, 1997; CD, 68 minutes
      - Recital, December 14, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 18)
        Lori Phillips, soprano; Mary Phillips, mezzo soprano; David Triestram, piano; Natasha Lipkin, viola.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, CD, 78 minutes
      - Recital, February 8, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 19)
        Shieh-Yih Lim, tenor; Martin Dubé, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 14, 1998; CD, 60 minutes
      - Recital, March 15, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 20)
        Sari Gruber, soprano; Cameron Stowe, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 21, 1998; CD, 71 minutes
      - Recital, April 5, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 21)
        Gregory Turay, tenor; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, April 11, 1998; CD, 64 minutes
      - Recital, May 17, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 22)
        Anne-Marie Seager, mezzo soprano; Yves Saelens, tenor; Kenneth Roberson, baritone; Stephen Philcox, piano; The Penderecki String Quartet.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 23, 1998; 2 CDs, 95 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 62 minutes
    - 1998-1999 Season
      - Recital, September 20, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 23)
        Nicole Heaston, soprano; Carol Anderson, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, September 26, 1998; 2 CDs, 81 minutes
      - Recital, October 18, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 24)
        Scott Hendricks, baritone; Steven Blier, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 24, 1998; 2 CDs, 53 minutes
      - Recital, November 15, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 25)
        Monique McDonald, soprano; Steven Blier, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 21, 1998; CD, 73 minutes
      - Recital, December 13, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 26)
        James Westman, baritone; Stephen Ralls, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 19, 1998; CD, 70 minutes
      - Recital, February 7, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 27)
        Bejun Mehta, countertenor; Warren Jones, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 13, 1999; CD, 64 minutes
      - Recital, March 14, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 28)
        Nikola Mijailovic, baritone; Giovanni Reggioli, piano.
        - WQXR radio broacast, March 20, 1999; CD, 74 minutes
      - Recital, April 25, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 29)
        Anne-Marie Seager, mezzo soprano; Joseph Lawson, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 15, 1999; CD, 69 minutes
      - Recital, May 23, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 30)
        Lester Lynch, baritone; Brian Farrell, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 29, 1999; 2 CDs, 86 minutes
    - 1999-2000 Season
      - Recital, September 26, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 31)
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 3, 1999; 2 CDs, 88 minutes
      - Recital, November 21, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 32)
        Daesan No, baritone; Laura Ward, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 27, 1999; CD, 67 minutes
      - Recital, December 12, 1999 (Box 139, Folder 33)
        Isabel Bayrakdarian, soprano; Carrie-Ann Matheson, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 18, 1999; CD, 44 minutes
      - Recital, February 13, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 34)
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 19, 2000; CD, 74 minutes
      - Recital, April 19, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 35)
        Stephanie Blythe, soprano; Warren Jones, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 74 minutes
      - Recital, May 14, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 36)
        Dina Kuznetsova, soprano; Alan Darling, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 20, 2000; 2 CDs, 82 minutes
    - 2000-2001 Season
      - Recital, September 24, 2000 (Box 140, Folder 1)
        Brian Leerhuber, baritone; Michael Baitzer, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, September 30, 2000; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, October 22, 2000 (Box 140, Folder 2)
        Jennifer Aylmer, soprano; J.J. Penna, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 67 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 28, 2000; CD, 57 minutes
      - Recital, November 12, 2000 (Box 140, Folder 3)
        Dean Ely, bass baritone; John Musto, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 18, 2000; CD, 57 minutes
      - Recital, December 17, 2000 (Box 140, Folder 4)
        Liesel Fedkenheuer, mezzo soprano; Miah Im, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, January 6, 2001; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, February 11, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 5)
        Charles Castronovo, tenor; Speranza Scappucci, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 17, 2001; CD, 57 minutes
      - Recital, March 4, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 6)
        On Wings of Song recital at Merkin Concert Hall, NYC.
        Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation, the Elaine Kaufman Cultural Center, the Kosciuszko Foundation, and WQXR-FM Radio.
        - Live recording, CD, 70 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 10, 2001; CD, 56 minutes
      - Recital, April 22, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 7)
        Jessica Tivens, soprano; William Ferguson, tenor; Lee Poulis, baritone; Maih Im, piano; Gresham/Cassidy Duo.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 79 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, April 28, 2001; CD, 54 minutes
      - Recital, June 3, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 8)
        Rinat Shaham, mezzo soprano; David Moody, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, June 9, 2001; CD, 56 minutes
    - 2001-2002 Season
      - Recital, September 30, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 9)
        Troy Cook, baritone; Kathleen Kelly, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 87 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 6, 2001; CD, 53 minutes
      - Recital, October 21, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 10)
        Eric Cutler, tenor; Israel Gursky, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 86 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 27, 2001; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, November 11, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 11)
        Erin Wood, soprano; Alan Darling, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 70 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 17, 2001; CD, 56 minutes
      - Recital, December 9, 2001 (Box 140, Folder 12)
        Nicolai Janitzky, baritone; Ines Irawati, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 78 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 15, 2001; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, February 10, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 13)
        Keith Phares, baritone; Michael Baitzer, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 74 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, February 16, 2002; CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, March 24, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 14)
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 88 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 30, 2002; CD, 57 minutes
      - Recital, April 14, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 15)
        Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation, the Elaine Kaufman Cultural Center, the Kosciuszko Foundation, and WQXR-FM Radio
        Lester Lynch, baritone; J.J. Penna, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 92 minutes
      - Recital, May 19, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 16)
        Meagan Miller, soprano; Kim Witman, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, June 1, 2002; CD, 57 minutes
    - 2002-2003 Season
      - Recital, September 29, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 17)
        Nmon Ford, baritone; Victoria Kirsch, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 74 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 5, 2002; CD, 47 minutes
      - Recital, October 20, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 18)
        Presenting the Marilyn Horne Foundation Awardees at the Music Academy of the West.
        Deborah Domanski, mezzo soprano; Jerome Tan, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 26, 2002; CD, 52 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 55 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 54 minutes
      - Recital, November 10, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 19)
        Encouragement Awardees 2002 Marilyn Horned Foundation Competition at the Music Academy of the West.
        Susanna Phillips, soprano; Justin Plank, baritone; Jerome Tan, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 79 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 59 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 70 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 70 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 69 minutes
      - Recital, December 15, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 20)
        Simon O'Neill, tenor; Michael Baitzer, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 59 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 21, 2002; CD, 57 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 63 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 63 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 62 minutes
      - Recital, February 16, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 1)
        Lauren Skuce, soprano; Jonathan Kelly, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 66 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 54 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 54 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 54 minutes
      - Recital, March 16, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 2)
        Keri Alkema, mezzo Soprano; Douglas Fisher, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 66 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 66 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 66 minutes
      - Recital, April 6, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 3)
        On Wings of Song recital at the Merkin Concert Hall at Kaufman Center, NYC.
        Twyla J. Robinson, soprano; Carol Isaac, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 55 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, April 12, 2003; CD, 59 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 1, VHS, 80 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 2, VHS, 71 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 1, DVD, 80 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 2, DVD, 71 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 1, Mini DV, 80 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 2, Mini DV, 71 minutes
      - Recital, May 7, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 4)
        Jennifer Aylmer, soprano; Troy Cook, baritone; Kathleen Kelly, piano; Kenneth Merrill, piano.
        - Live recording, 2 CDs, 85 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 17, 2003; CD, 60 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 164 minutes
        - Video recording - Two camera angles, 6 DVDs, 164 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 1, Mini DV, 87 minutes
        - Video recording - Camera angle 2, Mini DV, 86 minutes
    - 2003-2004 Season
      - Recital, October 5, 2003 (Box 141, Folder 5)
        Nathaniel Webster, baritone; Kevin Murphy, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 66 minutes
        - Live recording, CD, 72 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 18, 2003; CD, 59 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 65 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 65 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 66 minutes
      - Recital, November 9, 2003 (Box 142, Folder 1)
        John Matz, tenor; Carrie-Ann Matheson, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 78 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 22, 2003; CD, 57 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 77 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 77 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 77 minutes
      - Recital, December 7, 2003 (Box 142, Folder 2)
        Jennifer Check, soprano; Carrie-Ann Matheson, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 72 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 20, 2003; CD, 60 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 80 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 79 minutes
      - Recital, March 28, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 3)
        Jessica Jones, soprano; Mikael Eliasen, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 72 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 68 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 68 minutes
      - Recital, April 25, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 4)
        Megan Latham, mezzo soprano; Carol Wong, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 66 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 67 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 70 minutes
      - Recital, May 16, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 5)
        William Ferguson, tenor; Kenneth Merrill, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 72 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 29, 2004; CD, 56 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 79 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 81 minutes
    - 2004-2005 Season
      - Recital, October 17, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 6)
        On Wings of Song recital at St. Bartholomew's Church, NYC.
        Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and Great Music at St. Bartholomew's Church.
        Leonardo Capalbo, tenor; Jonathan Kelly, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 57 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 6, 2004; CD, 54 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 58 minutes
      - Recital, November 7, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 7)
        Susanna Phillips, soprano; Carol Wong, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 57 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 20, 2004; CD, 61 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
      - Recital, December 12, 2004 (Box 142, Folder 8)
        Barbara Quintiliani, soprano; Keri Alkema, mezzo soprano; Craig Terry, piano; Kari Jane Docter, cello.
        - Live recording, CD, 72 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, WXQR January 8, 2005; CD, unplayable
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 59 minutes
        - Video recording, DVD, 77 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 77 minutes
      - Recital, March 9, 2005 (Box 142, Folder 9)
        Garret Sorenson, tenor; Craig Terry, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 19, 2005; CD, 57 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 56 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 59 minutes
      - Recital, April 20, 2005 (Box 142, Folder 10)
        Andrew Garland, tenor; Donna Loewy, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 65 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, April 30, 2005; CD, 64 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 59 minutes
      - Recital, May 18, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 1)
        Erin Wall, soprano; Craig Rutenberg, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 59 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 58 minutes
    - 2005-2006 Season
      - Recital, September 25, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 2)
        Wendy Bryn Harmer, soprano; Carrie-Ann Matheson, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 70 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 08, 2005; CD, 55 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, November 6, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 3)
        Erica Strauss, soprano; Jerome Tan, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 19, 2005; CD, 58 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 59 minutes
      - Recital, December 4, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 4-5)
        2005 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awardees at the Music Academy of the West.
        Isabel Leonard, mezzo soprano; Tamara Sanikidze, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 66 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 17, 2005; CD, 62 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 64 minutes
        - Video recording - includes post recital carol singing, VHS, 83 minutes
        - Video recording - includes rehearsal and post recital carol singing, 2 Mini DV tapes, 101 minutes
      - Recital, March 12, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 6)
        Jesse Blumberg, baritone; Martin Katz, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 25, 2006; CD, 60 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, April 2, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 7)
        Quinn Kelsey, baritone; Craig Rutenberg, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 15, 2006; CD, 59 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 58 minutes
      - Recital, May 7, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 8)
        Alex Richardson, tenor; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 27, 2006; CD, 60 minutes
        - WFMT radio broadcast, CD, 57 minutes
        - Video recording, VHS, 63 minutes
        - Video recording, 2 Mini DVs, 62 minutes
    - 2006-2007 Season
      - Recital, October 13, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 9)
        On Wings of Song recital at Saint Louis Art Museum, MO.
        Ian Greenlaw, baritone; Peter Henderson, piano.
        - WQXR radio broadcast, January 13, 2007; CD, 56 minutes
      - Recital, October 29, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 10)
        Evan Hughes, bass baritone; Tamara Sanikidze, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 11, 2006; CD, 62 minutes
      - Recital, December 3, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 11)
        Richard Cox, tenor; Thomas Bagwell, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, December 16, 2006; CD, 60 minutes
      - Recital, February 25, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 12)
        Sidney Outlaw, baritone; Tamara Sanikidze, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 80 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, March 10, 2007; CD, 60 minutes
        - Video recording, 2 Mini DV tapes, 80 minutes
        - Video recording, Video files on DVD-R
      - Recital, March 25, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 13)
        On Wings of Song recital at The Santa Barbara Museum of Art, CA.
        Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and The Santa Barbara Museum of Art.
        - Live recording, CD, 80 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, April 14, 2007; CD, 59 minutes
      - Recital, April 22, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 14)
        Elaine Alvarez, soprano; John Churchwell, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, May 5, 2007; CD, 62 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 60 minutes
    - 2007-2008 Season
      - Recital, October 7, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 15)
        On Wings of Song recital at Christ and St. Stephen's Church, NYC.
        Jamie Barton, mezzo soprano; Kathleen Kelly, piano.
        - Live recording, CD, 73 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, October 20, 2007; CD, 62 minutes
        - Video recording, Mini DV, 70 minutes
      - Recital, October 14, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 16)
        - Live recording, CD, 79 minutes
        - WQXR radio broadcast, November 10, 2007; CD, 68 minutes
      - Recital, November 11, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 1)
        Nadine Sierra, soprano; Carrie-Ann Matheson, piano.